是谁
Who's there?!
谁在那儿
救命啊
Help!
你们想怎样
What do you want?!
《暮光之城3：月食》
有人说 世界将终结于火
Some say the world will end in fire.
有人说会葬送于冰
Some say in ice…
我曾尝过欲望之果
From what I've tasted of desire,
我赞同终结于火
I hold with those who favor fire.
但若非要两度沉沦
But if I had to perish twice…
我想我对仇恨了解够多
I think I know enough of hate,
可以说 如果是毁灭
To say that, for destruction,
葬送于冰也不错
Ice, is also great.
是个选择
And would suffice.
别闹了 我英语要期末考
You know, I've got an English final.
我得专心复习
I gotta focus.
嫁给我吧
Marry me.
转化我
Change me.
如果你嫁给我 我就答应
Okey I will if you marry me,
这叫做折衷
It's called a compromise.
这叫做强迫
It's just called coercion.
这不公平
It's not fair.
婚姻只不过是一纸证书
Marriage is just…is a piece of paper.
在我的时代 这是表明「我爱你」的方式
Where I am from, it's the way one says, "I love you".
在我的时代 我这个年纪
Where I come from, at my age…
结婚意味着「这孩子怀孕了」
It's the way one says, "I just got knocked up".
你是在意大家的看法
So, you're worried about what people will think.
三分之二的婚姻都以离婚收场
You know, it's two out of three marriages end in divorce.
我想 吸血鬼和人类结婚
Well, I think you'll find the…
他们的离婚率大概会低些
vampire, human divorce rate is a little lower.
- 嫁给我吧 - 我不能
- Just marry me. - I can't.
我四点要回去
I have to be back at four.
（华盛顿观察家）
（被杀 失踪 怀疑为连环杀手作案 乔治城小巷发现又一受害者）
四点准时回家
Four o'clock on the dot.
那孩子现在是想讨好我吗
That kid trying to brown nose me now or something?
人家有名字 你现在嫌他太守时了吗
He has a name. And now he's too punctual for you?
好吧
Okey…
你知道自己为什么被禁足 对吧
You understand why you're being punished, right?
知道 因为我太让你担心了
I know, I put you through hell.
没错 我担心死了
Yes, you did.
但我将你禁足有别的原因
But I have other reasons, for grounding you.
比如
Like…
我想让你和他保持一定距离
I just want you to get some separation from him.
爸爸 你不能这样
Dad, there is nothing you can say.
爱德华是我生命中的一部分
Edward is in my life.
是啊 这我十分清楚
Yeah, I'm gathering that.
好吧 不如这样
So, alright. How about this?
我们做个约定
I'll make you a deal.
我可以给你解除禁令
You're not grounded anymore,
如果你自由之后 也会去见其他朋友的话
If…You use your new found freedom…to see some of your other friends too,
比如说 见雅各布
Like…Like Jacob.
他如今的日子很不好过
He's going through a really tough time right now,
他爸爸很担心他
His Dad's really worried about him.
我记得 你伤心的时候
I remember when that was you.
需要朋友安慰 那时陪在你身边的是雅各
You needed a friend, Jake was there.
我是雅各 请留言
Hey, it's Jake.Leave a message.
雅各布好几周没理我了
Jacob hadn't talk to me in weeks.
我想要和好 可是他不给我机会
I wanted to fix it, he just…He wouldn't give me the chance.
你吓到我了
You scared me.
你现在要去保留地
You're going now to the reservation.
你怎么会知道
How'd you…
是爱丽丝预见的
Alice…
你们连我的车也盯着吗
Did you do this to my truck?
贝拉 你要理解
Bella, you have to understand.
你的安全就是我的一切
Your safety is everything to me.
雅各布绝不会伤害我的
Jacob is not gonna hurt me!
他不会有意伤害你 但狼人容易失控
Not intentionally, but the wolves have no control…
爱德华 直到毕业前 我都可以去见他
Edward!I have…until graduation, to see him.
之后我就会成为吸血鬼 他会永远恨我
And I'll be one of you, and he'll hate me forever.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
- 你们好 - 来得正好 听听这个
- Hey. - Just in time. Alright, check it out.
听听你要说什么
Alright, let's see what you got.
同学们 我们是未来的主人
My fellow students.We are the future.
只要你相信
Anything is possible…
- 一切皆有可能 - 不错
- …If you just believe. - Nice.
- 完美 - 准备个演讲稿吧
- Perfect. - And got yourself a speech.
不 要是拿这个当演讲稿
No, this will be my speech.
除非我想被大家丢来的毕业证砍死
When I want everyone to throw diplomas at my head.
谢谢你的好意
So…Thank you.
杰西你就守着这些陈词滥调吧
Ya gotta embrace the cliches, Jess.
这些陈词滥调 每个演说者都会说一遍
They have the bread and butter of all valedictorians.
所以你当不了毕业演讲代表
And that is why you are not valedictorian.
杰西不需要这些陈词滥调
And Jess doesn't need cliches.
你的演讲会很棒的
Speech is gonna be epic.
很棒 那会改写人生的
Epic? It'll change lives.
我打算开个派对
I decided to throw a party.
天知道我们还要从高中毕业多少次
After all, how many times we gonna graduate high school?
开派对 在你家吗
A party? At your place?
我从没去过你家
I've never seen your house.
从没有人去过他们家
No one's ever seen their house.
- 又要开派对吗 爱丽丝 - 会很好玩的
- Another party, Alice? - It'll be fun.
是啊 你上次也这么说
Yeah.That's what you said last time.
- 安吉拉 - 什么事
- Hey, Angela. - Yes.
需要帮忙吗
Do you need some help with those?
你知道她预见了什么 告诉我
I know you know what she saw. Tell me.
没什么事
It was nothing.
你在担心
You looked worried.
我只是担心大家看出爱丽丝的异常反应
Just that everyone would notice how strange Alice is.
都过去那么久了 不用担心
I think that ship sailed long ago.
我想知道出了什么事
I wonder what's wrong.
西雅图有个人失踪一年多了
There's someone missing in Seattle, over a year ago.
查理正在想办法 但是
Charlie is doing what he can, but…
你知道些什么
Do you know something about this?
我们一直在追踪西雅图的情况
We've been tracking the situation in Seattle for a while.
离奇失踪 不明原因死亡
Unexplained disappearances, killings…
如果事态再扩大的话
If the situation gets anymore conspicuous,
沃尔图里家族家族就会介入
the Volturi will step in.
如果他们去西雅图 就有可能来这里
If they go to Seattle, they can come here.
他们会发现 我还是人类
They can see I'm still human.
我们不会坐以待毙
We won't get that far.
如果有必要 我们会去西雅图
But we'll go to Seattle if we have to.
- 我会第一时间传真给你们 - 谢谢
- I'll fax these down the first thing. - Thank you.
- 可以去吃晚饭了吗 - 可以
- You're ready for dinner? - Yeah.
就我们两人一起吃晚饭 对吧
It is still just…you and I, alright?
是的 我只是顺路送她
No, I'm just dropping her off.
- 回头见 - 再见
- See you later. - Bye.
贝拉 我父母让我提醒你
Bella. My parents wanted to remind you about the…
不要忘了用生日那天送你的机票
airline ticket you got for your birthday.
什么机票
What airline ticket?
去佛罗里达州看妈妈的往返机票
A round trip ticket to see Mom in Florida.
真慷慨啊
That was generous.
马上就过期了 他们建议你这周末用掉
And it expires soon, they say you might wanna use it this weekend.
我不能抛下一切 说去就去啊
I can't just drop everything and go.
这也许是你毕业前最后一次见她的机会了
It might be your last chance to see her before you graduate.
这提议不错
It might not be a bad idea.
出城几天
Get out of the town for a couple of days,
分开一段时间
get some distance.
好吧 我可以去看妈妈
Yeah, I wouldn't mind seeing Mom…
但你要用情侣票和我一起去
As long as you use the companion ticket.
等等
Wait,
只有你们两个吗
just two tickets?
真想不到
Super,
这可让我高兴到死了
that makes me really happy.
我确实想去看看妈妈
I did wanna see my Mom.
我想看到她的生活美满幸福
I wanted to know that her life was full by satisfying.
你不怀念这感觉吗
Aren't you gonna miss this?
不怀念沐浴在阳光下的舒适感吗
Don't you just feel the vitamin D soaking up in your pores?
是啊 我会很怀念的
Yeah, I'm gonna miss this.
佛罗里达的大学阳光会更加明媚的
You know, colleges in Florida are a lot sunnier.
我只是说 如果你去阿拉斯加大学
I'm just saying, if you go to university of Alaska…
我就再也见不到你了
I'm never gonna see you.
他们的科研项目不错
They have a really great science program.
那个项目名称叫爱德华吗
You mean Edward program.
他看你的眼神
The way he watches you…
仿佛愿意跳到你面前
It's like he's willing to leap in front of you,
为你挡子弹一样
and take a bullet or something.
这不好吗
Is that a bad thing?
这是非常强烈的感情
It's an intense thing.
和他在一起 你也变得不同
You're different with him.
你们彼此吸引 像磁铁一样
If he moves, you move.Like magnets.
我说不清 我们只是
I don't know, we're just…
坠入爱河 我明白
In love.I get it.
我只想确定
I just want to make sure,
你做出了对的选择
you're making the right choices for you.
毕竟 要和他在一起的人是你
You know, cause you're the one who's gonna have to live with him.
好了 沉重的话题到此为止
Alright, enough with the heavy.
- 妈妈 - 祝贺你
- Mom. - Congraduation.
我不想花你的钱
I didn't want you to spending your money.
没花钱 快打开看看
I didn't, come on.
这是你所有的旧旅行T恤吗
Are these all our old trip T-shirts?
没错 拿出来看
Get out!
我都留着呢 能做一床很好的被子
I saved'em all.I thought they'd make a good quilt.
让你在阿拉斯加也不会冷
To keep you warm up in Alaska.
记得这个吗 恩桑那达
Remember this one?Ensanada.
- 蛇窖 - 没错
- The snake pit. - Yep.
但这个是我最喜欢的 看这
But this one is my favourite.Here…
缅因州的三头龙虾
The three-headed lobster in Maine.
这礼物太棒了
This is amazing.
宝贝 真高兴你能喜欢
No, honey. I'm glad you've like it.
我在想 等你长大 有了孩子
I just figured, you know, when you get older, have kids,
我们能再加上几件 也许能去
We can add to it.Maybe go visit…
看看世界上最大的番茄酱瓶之类的
the world's largest catsup bottle or something.
谢谢你 妈妈
Thanks.
你喜欢 我很高兴
I'm glad you like it.
我只是觉得 你在阿拉斯加的时候
I just thought, you should have.
有这东西就像我陪在你身边
a little piece of me, up there in Alaska.
- 妈妈 - 什么事
- Mom. - Yeah.
- 我很想你 - 宝贝 我也想你
- I miss you. - Honey. I miss you too.
你确定这是你看到她的地方吗
You sure this is where you saw her?
她就快到了
She's almost here.
在你左边
On your left!
等等 她进入他们的领地了
Wait! She's in their territory.
她要逃走了
She'll get away!
她跑不了
No she won't!
埃美特 不要去
Emmett, no!
你后悔去那里吗
Did you regret going?
没有
No.
能见到妈妈我很开心
It was really great to see my mom.
只是要告别真的很难
Just really hard saying goodbye.
你可以不用和她告别
It doesn't have to be goodbye.
这就是你让我去的原因吗
Is that why you ask me to go?
你以为我会改变主意
You thought I was gonna change my mind.
我一直这么希望
I'm always hoping for that.
怎么了
What?
如果我要你留在车里 你会听吗
If I asked you to stay in the car, would you?
当然不会
Of course not.
查理说你出城了
Charlie said you left town.
是的 去看我妈妈 出什么事了
Yeah. To visit my Mom, why?
他只是想证实你还是人类
Just checking to see if you're still human.
我是来警告你的
I'm coming here to warn you.
如果你们再到我们的领地上来
If your kind come on our land again…
等等 怎么回事
Wait, what?
- 你没告诉她吗 - 别插手 雅各布
- You didn't tell her? - Just leave it alone, Jacob.
告诉我什么
Tell me what?
埃美特和保罗有点误会
Emmett and Paul had a misunderstanding,
没什么好担心的
there is nothing to worry about.
说得轻巧
Listen to you.
她出城也是被你骗出去的吗
Did you lie to get her out of town, too?
你该离开了 现在就走
You should leave.Now.
她有权利知道
She has a right to know.
她是红发吸血鬼要抓的那个
She is the one the red-head wants.
你是说维多利亚吗
Victoria?
爱丽丝预见的是她
Alice's vision.
我想要保护你
I was trying to protect you.
所以就对我撒谎
By lying to me.
好吧 这件事我们以后再谈 可是
Okey. We're gonna talk about this, but…
你
You!
你为什么不回我电话
Why haven't you called me back?
我无话可说
I had nothing to say.
可我有好多话要说 等等
I have tons. Hold on.
贝拉
Bella.
爱德华 你要相信我
Edward, you have to trust me.
我相信你
I do trust you.
可我不相信他
It's him I don't trust.
别太得意 雅各布 我们只是去兜一圈
Lose the grin, Jacob.We're just going for a ride.
扶稳了
Hold on tight.
你觉得这样好吗
Are you sure, this is a good idea?
别忘了 我是「吸血鬼女孩」
I'm a "vampire girl", remember?
- 看看谁回来了 - 贝拉 你还好吗
- Look who's back. - What's up, Bella?
- 奎尔 你呢 - 很好 终于加入大伙儿了
- Quil, you too? - Yep. Finally made the pack.
贝拉 真高兴你来了
I'm glad you're here, Bella.
我们总算不用听
Maybe we can get a break.
雅各没完没了的内心独白了
from Jake's obsessive inner monologue.
我希望贝拉打电话来
"I wish Bella would call."
我不希望贝拉打电话来
"I wish Bella wouldn't call".
也许我该给贝拉打电话
"Maybe I should call Bella".
也许我该给贝拉打电话 然后挂断
"Maybe I should call Bella and hang up".
好了 你们都闭嘴吧
Alright, you can shut up now.
贝拉 这是莉亚·克里尔沃特 哈利的女儿
Bella, this is Leah Clearwater.Harry's daughter.
你好 对于你父亲的死 我很遗憾
Hey.I'm really sorry about your father.
如果你是来这里折磨雅各布的
If you're here to torture Jacob some more,
那就请离开吧
feel free to leave.
她真有意思 是吧
Fun, isn't she?
贝拉 好久不见
Bella… Hi.
我一直在想什么时候能再见到你
I was wondering when we'd see your face around here again.
我也是
Yeah, same here.
山姆 一切都好吗
Sam, we're good?
一切都好
We're good.
她现在不会轻易越界了
She won't be getting through our line anytime soon.
莉亚什么时候加入的
So, when did Leah joined the pack?
大概在他父亲死后
Around when her Dad died.
她的弟弟赛斯也变身了
Her brother Seth, also phased.
他才15岁 是我们中最小的成员之一
He's only fifteen. One of the youngest we've had.
山姆一直让他在家学习 但他对此十分不满
Sam keeps him home studying, but he's chomping at the bit.
真希望加入的不是莉亚
Wish it was Leah who'd stay home.
得了 别大男子主义
Come on, don't be such a guy.
不 不是因为她是女生
No, it's… It's not a chick thing.
而是 三角关系太复杂了
It's… You know, a triangle thing.
莉亚 山姆和艾米粒三人的痛苦 我们感同身受
We all have to live the Leah, Sam, Emily pain-fest.
还记得我说的狼人的心理感应吗
Wolf telepathy, remember?
你是说 山姆为了艾米粒抛弃了莉亚
So, Sam dumps Leah for Emily?
不是那样
It wasn't like that.
山姆为伤害莉亚而痛恨自己
Sam hates himself for hurting Leah.
但艾米粒是他的真命天女
But, Emily was The One.
是啊 我想有时是要做出选择
Yeah, I guess it's sort of chooses you sometimes.
不仅仅是喜欢而已 贝拉
It's more than some crush, Bella.
艾米粒是山姆的烙印爱人
Sam imprinted on Emily.
什么意思
Do I want to know what that is?
烙印的爱是指
Imprinting on someone is like…
当你看到她 一切都变得不同
Like when you see her, everything changes.
突然之间
All of a sudden,
把你捆绑在地球上的不是重力
it's not gravity holding you to the planet.
而是她
It's her.
其他的事情不再重要
Nothing else matters.
你愿意为她做任何事
You would do anything…
变成任何样子
be anything for her.
听起来好像你知道那种感觉
It sounds like you know the feeling.
你有没有烙印爱人
Have you imprinted on someone?
如果我有 你会知道的
You'd know if I had.
我只是对山姆有直接感应
I just have a direct line to Sam's thoughts.
那就是说 你 还是原来的你
So for now, you're… still you.
- 你也是原来的你 - 没错
- And you're still you.- Yeah.
直到毕业
Until graduation.
毕业
Graduation?
你知道终究会发生的
You knew this was gonna happen.
但不是在一个月后
Not in a month!
我是说 不能在你 在你还活着就
I mean, not before you've… you've even lived!
或者在我可以
Or before I could…
有那么一秒 就一秒 我以为
For a second, just a second, I thought…
但是他让你陷得那么深
But he's got his hooks in you so deep.
我自己的决定 与他无关
I decided this, not him.
贝拉 他们甚至都不是活人
Bella, they're not even alive!
真让我恶心
It makes me sick!
我宁愿你死了也比变成他们好
Better you really be dead than one of them.
不敢相信你居然那么说
I can't believe you said that.
爱德华是对的 我不该来
Edward was right, I shouldn't have come.
贝拉 拜托 别走
Bella, come on. Please.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你知道
You know…
爱德华起码也该尊重下晚饭时间
Edward could at least respect meal times.
我和雅各在一起
I was just with Jake.
噢 那敢情好
Oh… Good.
那我给你们一些私人空间
I'll just give you two some privacy then.
你知道我有多担心吗
Do you understand how worried I've been?
我很安全
I was perfectly safe.
我差点就打破协约以确保你的安全
I almost break the treaty to make sure of it.
我知道 身上有狗味儿 对不起
I know, I smell like a dog. I'm sorry.
不 不是 有点不对劲
No, no. Something's wrong.
爱德华 怎么了
Edward, what's wrong?
有人来过
Someone's been in here.
是谁 我们认识吗
Who was it? Someone we know?
陌生人 我不认识他的气味
Just a stranger. I didn't recognize his scent.
过路的流浪者
A nomad passing through?
过路者是不会让贝拉的父亲活着的
A passer-by wouldn't have left Bella's father alive.
他的气味在贝拉家以南五英里处消失了
His scent disappeared about five miles south of Bella's house.
- 是有预谋的 - 维多利亚
- Someone's orchestrating this.- Victoria?
我没看到她做这个决定
I would've seen her deciding.
肯定是沃尔图里家族
It has to be the Volturi.
我想也不是沃尔图里家族
I don't think it's the Volturi either.
我也一直监视着埃罗的举动
I've been watching Aro's decisions, too.
那我们接着搜寻
So we keep looking.
并轮班守护贝拉和她家
We also take shifts, guarding Bella at her house.
- 又一个保护差事 - 罗莎莉
- Another protection detail?- Rosalie.
不 她说得很对
No, she's right.
你们不能一边保护我 看护我爸爸
You can't protect me, watch my dad…
又同时搜捕入侵者
and search for the intruder.
加上找维多利亚
And for Victoria.
还要喂饱你们自己
And keep yourselves fed.
我不能让你毫无保护
I'm not leaving you here defenseless.
可是 我也不能让你饿着
Well, I'm not gonna let you starve.
再说我不会是毫无保护的 我有
And I wouldn't be unprotected, I have…
你有什么
What?
不管是谁 他的气味留下了
Whoever it was, he left his stink behind.
下次碰到一定不会放过他的
It'll be hard to miss when we cross it again.
- 我们就从这入手 - 不需要你插手
- We'll handle it from here.- We don't need you to handle anything.
不需要任何人插手
Or anyone.
我才不管你需不需要
I could care less what you need.
很好 我们不干了
Alright, we're done here.
- 你才不干了 - 停
- No, you're done here.- Stop!
我很烦这样
I'm tired of this.
从现在开始我中立 行不行
From now on I'm Switzerland, Okay?
爱德华不喜欢这个主意
Edward hated the idea,
但是这已无关竞争
but it wasn't about rivalry anymore.
而是事关我和查理的安全
It was about my safety, and Charlie's.
接下来几天我好歹让他们能够合作了
In the days that followed I got them to at least try to work together.
狼人们接班
The wolves took over.
这样卡伦一家可以去捕食
so the Cullen's can hunt.
这真不是什么和睦的联盟
It wasn't exactly an easy alliance.
他连件上衣都没有吗
Doesn't he own a shirt?
我在这里很好了 你走吧
I'm good here, you should go.
我不会走远的
I'm not gonna be going long.
别急 你需要好好捕食
Don't rush. You need to hunt.
还是稍微急一点点吧
Maybe you rush a little bit.
- 嗨 美女 - 嗨
- Hey, beautiful.- Hi.
那么 今天想做什么
So, what ya wanna do today?
骑车 散步 闲逛 听你的
Bike, hike, hang? Your call.
或者我们今晚去个聚会
Or we're going to a party tonight.
你确定这样行吗
You sure this is okay?
我真的不喜欢做聚会的不速之客
I really hate being a party crasher.
严格来说 你是个商讨会的不速之客
Technically, you're a Council Meeting crasher.
瞧 会议领袖 爸爸 奎尔的爷爷 还有苏·克里尔沃特
See. The Council leaders, Dad, Quil's grandpa, and Sue Clearwater.
哈利死后她接的班
She took over for Harry when he died.
好吧 我其实不该来的
Okay, I should not be here.
没什么的 我想
You're okay. I thought…
我是说 他们认为你应该听听这些历史
I mean, they thought it would be good for you to hear the histories.
历史
The histories?
部落的历史 不是机密的吗
The tribe's histories? Aren't they secret?
我们都身居其中 你也是
We all got a role to play. And you're a part of this.
我是说 这也是赛斯莉亚和奎尔第一次聆听历史
I mean, it's the first time Seth, Leah and Quil are hearing them, too.
只不过你是有史以来第一个外人
But you are the first outsider. Ever.
不是要我早知道了 我才不相信你
If I haven't known that, I wouldn't believe you.
- 也会穿得好一点 - 雅各
- And would've dressed better.- Jake.
- 嗨 - 你来的正是时候
- Hey.- It's about time, you got here.
保罗把吃的都干掉了
Paul's been hoovering the grub.
不过我给你留了些汉堡
But, I saved you some burgers.
真是雪中送炭啊 老弟
Good looking out, Bro.
贝拉 这是赛斯·克里尔沃特 莉亚的弟弟
Bella, this is Seth Clearwater, Leah's brother.
族群的最新成员
Newest member of the pack.
最新的 最好的 最聪明的
Newest, bestest, brightest.
也是速度最慢的
And slowest.
- 来嘛 你爸爸马上就开始了 - 好
- Come on. Your dad's about to start.- Alright.
奎鲁特族在一开始只是个很小的部落
The Quileutes have been a small tribe from the beginning…
但我们的血液中流淌着魔力
But we've always had magic in our blood.
我们是杰出的精神斗士
We were great spirit warriors.
能够变成强大的狼的变形者
shape shifters, that transform into the powerful wolf.
这让我们能够吓走敌人
This enabled us to scare off our enemies,
保护我们的部落
and protect our tribe.
有一天我们的勇士遇到了
One day our warriors came across.
一种生物
a creature…
它看起来是人类 可是却坚硬如磐石
It looked like a man, but it was hard like stone,
冷似冰
and cold as ice…
我们勇士的尖牙最终让它四分五裂
Our warriors' sharp teeth, finally tore it apart.
但是只有火才能将它彻底摧毁
But only fire would completely destroy it.
族人生活在恐惧之中
They lived in fear,
那个吸血鬼绝不是孤身一人
the Cold Man was not alone.
他们猜对了
And they were right.
她将仇恨倾泻到整个村庄
She took her vengeance out on the village.
我们的祖先领袖 塔哈·阿吉
Our elder chief, Taha Aki,
是留下来拯救部落的唯一的精神斗士
was the only spirit warrior left to save the tribe,
因为他的儿子死去了
after his son was killed.
塔哈·阿吉的第三个妻子看出他快输了
Taha Aki's Third Wife could sees that he would lose…
第三个妻子是普通人类
The Third Wife was no magical being,
没有特殊的力量 但是她有
no special powers, but one…
勇气
Courage.
第三个妻子牺牲自己的鲜血
The Third Wife's sacrifice.
分散了女吸血鬼的注意力
distracted the Cold Woman,
足以让塔哈·阿吉毁灭了她
long enough for Taha Aki to destroy her.
她拯救了部落
She saved the tribe.
随着时间的推移 我们的敌人逐一消失
Over time, our enemies have disappeared.
但有一种留存了下来
But one remains…
就是吸血鬼
The Cold Ones.
每当它们靠近 我们的魔力就会苏醒
Our magic awakens when they near.
我们现在就感受到了
And we sense it now,
血液里感到了威胁
we feel the threat in our blood.
灾难即将来临
Something terrible is coming.
我们必须有所准备 所有的人
And we must all be ready. All of us.
你对我做了什么
What did you do to me?
- 我好 - 是啊 我知道
- I'm so…- Yeah, I know…
我们会给你找个人喝喝的
We'll find you someone to drink.
保护好自己不要被杀 明白吗
Just try not to get killed, will you?
我还需要人手
I'm gonna need numbers.
西雅图被恐惧笼罩
Seattle is in a state of terror…
警方为急剧增多的谋杀案与失踪案而不解
Police are baffled by the escalating murders and disappearances.
人们猜测 或许是残暴的新帮派
Theories range from a vicious new gang.
或许是异常活跃的连环杀手犯案
to a wildly active serial killer…
- CNN记者唐·楚白现场报道 - 事情在恶化
- Reporting live, Dawn Chubai. CNN. - It's getting worse.
我们必须要采取行动
We're going to have to do something.
只有一个吸血鬼肯定是做不出这种破坏的
It takes more than one of our kind to cause the damage they're reporting.
除非他们人数很多
Quite a few more.
没有章法 惹人注意
They're undisciplined, conspicuous…
他们是新生儿
It's Newborns.
什么 新生的吸血鬼吗
What, like new vampires?
在他们变化后的头几个月
In their first few months after they change.
是最难控制的时候
That's when we're at our most uncontrollable,
因饥渴而疯狂难训
Vicious, insane with thirst.
总是在渴盼
Something to look forward to.
没有人训练这些新生儿
No one has trained these newborns,
但这绝对不是偶然的
but this isn't random.
有人在制造吸血鬼军队
Someone's creating an army.
现在我们必须去西雅图了
Oh, now we definitely going to Seattle.
吸血鬼军队
An Army of vampires?
它们是被制造出来战斗的
And they've been created to fight someone.
我们是离西雅图最近的部族
We're the only clan even close to Seattle.
不管它们是从哪里来的
Regardless, of who are they were may,
如果我们不阻止他们
if we don't put a stop to them,
沃尔图里家族会来的
the Volturi will.
我很诧异他们居然放任不管这么久
I'm surprised they've let it go on this long.
也许他们正是幕后黑手
Maybe they're behind it.
在意大利 我读到了埃罗的想法
In Italy, I read Aro's mind…
他想要我和爱丽丝入伙
He wants me and Alice to join him…
他知道只要我们的家族还在
He knows we'd never choose him.
我们就不会同意的
as long as our family is still alive.
一支军队可以替他解决这个问题
An army could solve that for him.
寻人启事
Riley Biers.
嗨 吃晚饭了吗
Hey. Did you eat dinner yet?
还没
Um… no… I haven't.
这个小孩儿莱利·比尔斯
This kid Riley Biers,
一年前失踪了
disappeared over a year ago.
他可怜的父母从那时起
And his poor parents been papering Seattle.
把这个贴满了西雅图
with these things ever since.
你是不是觉得他们还是放弃了好
You think they should just give up?
不 如果失踪的是你
I wouldn't. If it were you…
我永远不会停止找你
Not ever.
我还没想好怎么告诉大家
I have to figure out what to tell people…
为什么圣诞不回家了
Why I won't be home for Christmases.
为什么我不再拜访他们
Why I won't visit.
为什么他们再也见不到我
Why they'll never see me again.
几十年后 你认识的人都会死去
After a few decades, everyone you know will be dead.
问题就解决了
Problem solved.
为什么你如此反对我变成吸血鬼
Why are you so against me becoming like you?
我告诉过你
I've told you.
不要骗我 肯定还有别的理由
Be honest with me. There's more.
我知道 你所做的选择会带来的后果
I know the consequences, of this choice you're making.
我曾经历过
I've lived through it,
现在再让你去受这个罪
and to let you suffer that.
你总相信我是有灵魂的
You believe I have a soul…
我没有
I don't.
之所以冒险同意你的选择
But to risk yours,
是为了永远不会失去你
just for the sake of never having to lose you.
这是我做过最自私的事了
It's the most selfish thing I'll ever do.
我以为 你可能是怕我会变得太不一样
I thought, maybe you were afraid that I'll be too different.
不一样 我不会再
Unlike. I won't be,
你知道 温暖
you know… warm.
而且气味也会不一样了
And won't smell the same.
你永远都是我的贝拉
You'll always be my Bella.
我的贝拉 坚强了
My Bella, just less fragile.
天啊 这里好漂亮
Gosh, it's so pretty here.
爱丽丝在策划一个盛大的毕业舞会
So, Alice is planning a big graduation party,
你也被邀请了
which you're invited to.
好吧 我就知道
Yeah, I figured that.
怎么了
What?
我其实想用不同的方式
I just wanted to do this differently.
更愉悦的方式
Smoother.
但如今 没有那么多时间了
But now, I'm out of time.
干嘛
To what?
你必须知道真相 贝拉
You need to hear the truth, Bella.
看清你的选择
Understand all your options.
你要知道
And you need to know…
我爱你
that I'm in love with you.
我希望你选择的是我 而不是他
And I want you to choose me, instead of him.
我以为你明白
I thought you understood.
- 我对你没有那种感觉 - 我不相信
- I don't feel that way for you.- I don't buy it.
你不相信什么
What don't you buy?
这就是我的感觉
That's how I feel.
你对我还有别的感觉
You feel something else for me,
只是你不愿意承认
you just won't admit it.
所以我不会放弃的 我要争取你
So I'm not giving up. I'm gonna fight for you.
直到你的心脏停止跳动
Until your heart stops beating.
那好 你倒不会争取太久的
Well, then you're not gonna have to fight for long.
你急着改变是因为你害怕自己会改变想法
You're rushing into it because you're afraid you'll change your mind.
不 我没有
No, I'm not.
我知道我想要什么
I know what I want.
跟了我不需要改变 贝拉
You wouldn't have to change for me, Bella.
也不用跟任何人永别
Or say goodbye to anybody.
我能给你的比他更多
I can give you more than him.
我是说 他甚至都不能随心所欲地吻你
I mean, he probably can't even kiss you without hurting you.
感觉到了吗
Feel that?
血肉之躯和温暖
Flesh and blood and warmth.
爱德华
Edward!
如果你再敢乱来
If you ever touch her against her will again!
不要这样
Don't do this!
她根本就不确定自己想要什么
She's not sure what she wants!
- 不要这样 - 好 那我给你个提示
- Don't do this!- Well, let me give you a clue!
等她把话说完
Wait for her to say the words!
行啊 就好像她真有话要说一样
Fine! And she will!
雅各布 你走吧
Jacob. Just go, okay!
行了小伙们 别打 停一停 好吧
Easy guys, easy. Let's take it down a notch. Alright?
出什么事儿了
What's going on?
我吻了贝拉
I kissed Bella.
她的手还受伤了
And she broke her hand…
打我脸弄的
punching my face.
全都是误会
Total misunderstanding.
扭伤而已 很快就会好的
It's just a sprain, should heal fairly quickly.
又一边走路一边嚼口香糖了吗
Trying to walk and chew gum at the same time again, Bella?
- 我揍了狼人的脸 - 坏蛋
- I punched a werewolf in the face. - Bad ass…
你会是个难缠的新生儿
You're gonna be one tough little newborn.
对付你是没问题的
Tough enough to take you on.
没事的
Don't worry about it.
好了 有线索吗
Okay, any Leads?
没有入侵者的迹象 但维多利亚不断出现
No sign of the intruder. But Victoria continues to make appearances.
找别人谈论成为新生儿的喜悦去
Go blather to someone else about the joys of becoming a newborn.
好吧 罗莎莉
Okay. Rosalie…
我不明白我做了什么让你这么恨我
I don't understand what I did, to make you hate me so much.
我不恨你
I don't hate you.
我也不是很喜欢你 但是
I don't particularly like you, but…
- 贝拉 我嫉妒你 - 什么
- Bella, I envy you. - What?
- 太荒谬了 - 一点也不
- That's ridiculous. - No, it's not.
你有选择 我当初没有
You have a choice. I didn't.
我们都没有 但你有 而你却选错了
None of us did. But you do, and you're choosing wrong.
我不在乎作为人类的你生活有多凄惨
I don't care how miserable your human life is.
我的生活不凄惨
My life is not miserable.
我的生活不完美 但没人的生活是完美的
It's not perfect, but nobody's life is perfect.
我曾经的生活是 绝对的完美
Mine was. Absolutely perfect.
我现在还希望得到那一切
Everything as I still wanted.
结婚 有一所大房子
To be married, With a nice house and.
丈夫会在我回家时吻我
a husband…to kiss me when he came home.
我自己的家庭
A family of my own.
罗伊斯·金是当时镇上最合适的单身汉
Royce King was the most eligible bachelor in town.
我对他知之甚少
I barely knew him.
但我那么年轻 我爱上的只是爱情
But I was young. I was in love with the idea of love.
我生命中的最后一天 我很晚才离开朋友家
On the last night of my life, I left a friend's house late.
- 我快到家时 - 她来了
- I wasn't far from home. - Here she is.
罗莎 过来
Hey, Rose! Come over here!
给 拿着这个
Here, hold this.
过来 我们一直在等你
Hey, come over here. We've been waiting for you.
她来了
Here she is.
罗伊斯
Royce.
你喝醉了
You're drunk.
她多可爱啊 约翰 我告诉过你她长得很俊
Isn't she lovely, John? I told you she was a looker.
她穿着那么多衣服 很难说啊
It's hard to say with all those clothes on.
你说呢 罗莎 不如我们脱掉几层
What do you say, Rose? Why don't we take off a few layers?
住手
Stop it!…
明天等你清醒了 我们再见
I'll see you tomorrow. Sober.
等等 你以为你能去哪
Hey, where do you think you're going?
住手 不要 放开我 住手
Stop it! Just stop it! Let go! Stop it!
给我回来 照我说的做
Comeback! Hey, you'll do as I say!
他们把我丢在大街上 以为我已经死了
They left me in the street, thinking I was dead.
相信我 我倒希望自己死了
Believe me, I wanted to be.
卡莱尔发现了我 他闻到了血的味道
Carlisle found me, he smelled all the blood…
- 他以为他是在救我 - 我很抱歉
- Thought he was helping me. - I'm sorry.
不过我还是报了仇
I got my revenge on them.
一次一个
One at a time.
罗伊斯留在最后 这样他可以知道我要来
I saved Royce for last, so he'd know I was coming.
我当年有些戏剧化
I was a little theatrical back then.
我找到埃美特后情况就好些了
Things got better after I found Emmett.
但是我们永远都只能是这样
But we'll always be this.
冰冷的 永远无法改变
Frozen, never moving forward.
那是我最怀念的 无尽的可能
That's what I miss the most, the possibilities.
坐在某处的门廊上
Sitting on a front porch somewhere,
埃美特坐在我身边 头发花白
Emmett gray haired by my side,
周围还有我们的孙子孙女
surrounded by our grandchildren,
和他们的笑声
their laughter.
我明白 那是你想要的
I understand, that's what you want.
但我想要的永远只有
But there's nothing I'll ever gonna want, more…
爱德华
than Edward.
你又错了
You're wrong again.
在你被转变之后 有样东西你会更想要
After you've been changed, there's one thing you'll want more…
你会为之杀戮
One thing you'll kill for…
血
Blood.
我说过什么 低调行事
What did I say, about low profile?
有什么要来了
Something's coming…
他们比你我任何一个都强大
Something… Bigger than any of us alone.
如果你们不能
And if you can't…
控制自己
control yourselves…
我们就只有死路一条
We're all going to die.
事已至此
What's done is done, just…
做好善后
clean up after yourselves.
他们已经吸引了太多的注意
They've already drawn too much attention.
我们的无所作为也一样
So has our "Inaction".
其他人也许已经开始质疑沃尔图里家族的效率
Others may begin to question the Volturi's effectiveness.
随他们去
Let them.
也许我们应该咨询下埃罗
Maybe we should consult with Aro.
埃罗的抉择已经被监视
Aro's decisions are being watched.
必须由我们决定
We must decide.
那就做出抉择吧 是时候了
Then decide sister. It's time.
没错
Yes, it is.
或者 我们让他们完成自己的使命
Either we let them do what they were created for…
或者 我们消灭他们
Or we end them.
抉择啊抉择
Decisions, decisions…
我们五岁时
When we were five,
人们问我们长大后想做什么
they asked us what we wanted to be when we grew up…
我们的回答是宇航员 总统之类的
Our answers were things like astronaut, president…
或者以我来说 一位公主
Or in my case, a princess.
当我们十岁时 他们又问一次
When we were ten, they asked again,
我们回答 摇滚明星 牛仔
and we answered, rock star, cowboy,
或者以我来说 金牌得主
or in my case, a gold medalist.
但是现在我们长大了 他们想要真正的答案
But now that we've grown up, they want a serious answer.
这个怎么样
Well, how about this…
谁他妈知道
who the hell knows?
现在不是做出艰难而仓促决定的时候
This isn't the time to make hard and fast decisions,
现在是犯错误的时候
this is the time to make mistakes.
登上错误的列车 困在某处
Take the wrong train and get stuck somewhere.
坠入爱河 一次又一次
Fall in love, a lot.
主修哲学 因为那是最没前途的专业
Major in philosophy, because there's no way to make a career out of that.
改变主意 再反悔 因为没有什么是永恒的
Change your mind, and change it again, because nothing is permanent.
所以 尽可能地去犯错
So, make as many mistakes as you can.
那样 有一天 当他们问我们想做什么时
That way, someday, when they ask what we wanna be…
我们不需要再猜测 因为已经了然于心
we won't have to guess. We'll know.
你做到了
You've made it!
你觉得我的演讲怎么样
What'd you think of my speech?
太像广告 励志书籍之类的吗 说吧
Too easy-breezy, too self-helpful? You may admit it.
不会 你干得很好
No, you pretty much nailed it.
我天生就是做领袖的料 对吧
It's like I was born to lead, right?
我喜欢这首歌 去跳舞吧
Oh, great. I love this song, let's go.
- 你在这干什么 - 你邀请我来的 记得吗
- What are you doing here? - You invited me, remember?
我的右勾拳就那么无力吗
Was my right hook too subtle for you?
那就是我告诉你不要来了
That was me uninviting you.
贝拉 我很抱歉
Look, Bella. I'm sorry… about, you know…
那个吻 还有你的手
The kiss and your hand…
我可以说是兽性作祟
I'd blame it on the whole inner animal thing…
但其实只是我 混蛋的我
But it was really just… me. Being an ass.
我真的抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我带了点东西给你
I brought you something.
毕业礼物 我自己做的
A graduation present. I made it myself.
你亲手做的
Oh… You made this?
很漂亮 谢谢
It's really pretty. Thanks.
等我一下
I'll be right back.
- 爱丽丝 你看到什么了 - 决定已经作出
- Alice, what did you see? - The decision's been made.
- 怎么回事 - 你们不去西雅图了吗
- What's going on? - You're not going to Seattle?
不了
No…
他们朝这里来了
They're coming here.
四天后就到
They'll be here in four days.
这会是一场恶战
This could turn into a blood bath.
- 谁指使的 - 没看到认识的
- Who's behind it? - I didn't see anyone I recognize.
也许有一个
Maybe one…
我知道他 他是本地人 莱利·比尔斯
I know his face. He's local, Riley Biers.
这不是他挑起的
He didn't start this.
无论是谁 都只是在暗处
Whoever did is staying out of the action.
他们利用了你预知能力的盲点
They must be playing with the blind spots in your vision.
无论如何 军队已经来了
Either way, the army is coming…
我们的人数不足以保护这个镇子
and there aren't enough of us to protect the town.
等等 什么军队
Hold up! What damn army?
- 新生儿 吸血鬼 - 他们的目标是什么
- Newborns. Our kind. - What are they after?
他们在辨识贝拉的味道
They were passing around Bella's scent.
一件红衬衣
A red blouse.
他们的目标是贝拉
They're after Bella?
- 那是什么意思 - 意味着一场恶战
- What the hell does this mean? - It means an ugly fight.
和牺牲
With lives lost.
好吧
Alright…
- 我们加入 - 不行
- We're in. - No.
你们会被杀的 不可能
You'll get yourselves killed, noway.
- 我不是在征求许可 - 爱德华
- I wasn't asking for permission. - Edward.
这意味着你有更多的保护
It means more protection for you.
雅各布 你觉得山姆愿意达成共识吗
Jacob. Do you believe Sam will agree to… an understanding?
只要我们能杀掉几只吸血鬼
As long as we get to kill some vampires.
- 贾斯帕 - 他们可以增加我们的胜算
- Jasper? - They'll give us the numbers.
那些新生儿都不知道他们的存在
And the newborns won't know they even exist.
- 那就是我们的优势 - 我们需要协调一下
- That'll give us an edge. - We'll need to coordinate.
卡莱尔 他们会受伤的
Carlisle, they'll gonna get hurt.
我们都需要训练
We'll all need some training.
与新生儿作战需要学习贾斯帕的经验
Fighting newborns requires knowledge that Jasper has.
欢迎加入
You're welcome to join us.
很好 时间地点你定
Alright. Name the time and place.
雅各
Jake…
你不知道你自己卷进了什么
You don't know what you're getting yourself in to.
贝拉
Bella…
我们这么做 你应该高兴才是
This is what we do. You should be happy.
看看我们 并肩作战
Look at us, working together.
是你希望我们和睦相处的 记得吗
You're the one who wanted us to get along, remember?
再来
Again!
只是毕业礼物
It's a graduation present.
若是信任我们 他们应该以人形现身
They don't trust us enough to be in their human forms.
他们来了 那就行
They came. That's what matters.
你来做翻译
Will you translate?
嗨 雅各
Hey, Jake.
欢迎
Welcome.
贾斯帕有和新生儿打交道的经验
Jasper has experience with newborns.
他会教我们如何击败他们
He'll teach us how to defeat them.
他们想知道新生儿和我们有什么不同
They want to know how the "Newborns" Is differ from us.
他们比我们要强壮许多倍
They're a great deal stronger than us,
他们自己的血液还残留在身体组织里
because their own human blood lingers in their tissues.
吸血鬼的能力在转变后的
Our kind is never more physically powerful…
最先几个月最厉害
than in our first several months of this life.
卡莱尔说得没错
Carlisle's right.
所以他们才会诞生
That's why they are created.
一支新生儿大军
A newborn army,
不需要像人类军队那样需要几千人
doesn't need thousands like a human army.
也没有人类军队可以阻挡他们
And no human army could stand against them.
有两件事需要记住 第一
The two most important things to remember are, first…
绝不要让他们的胳膊环住你
Never let them get their arms around you.
他们可以瞬间将你压碎 第二
They'll crush you instantly. The second…
不要想一击毙命
Never go for the obvious kill.
他们就等着你那么做 你只会输
They'll be expecting that. And you will lose.
埃美特
Emmett?
- 放开手脚 - 没问题
- Don't hold back. - Not in my nature.
绝不要放松警惕
Never lose focus.
还有一件事
One more thing…
不要轻视你的敌人
Never turn your back on your enemy.
你们中的某些人会受伤
Some of you, are gonna get hurt.
甚至会死 都因为我
Some of you could get killed, because of me.
到时候会比这个激烈一百倍 对吗
It's gonna be a hundred times worse than this, right?
今天到此为止
We're done for the day.
贾斯帕
Jasper…
你确定没有我能帮忙的地方吗
Are you sure, there's nothing I can do to help?
只要你出现就足够了
Your presence alone,
你的味道会分散新生儿的注意力
your scent will distract the newborns.
他们的猎杀本性会占上风 把他们逼疯
Their hunting instinct will take over, drive them crazy.
很好 很高兴知道
Good. I'm glad.
等等
Hey.
你怎么会知道这么多
How do you know so much about this?
我成长的经历跟我的兄弟姐妹不大一样
I didn't have quite the same upbringing as my adopted siblings.
这些咬痕跟我的一样
Those bites are like mine.
战斗时留下的
Battle scars.
我在南方军接受的所有训练
All the training the Confederate Army gave me…
在新生儿面前都是无用的
was useless against the newborns.
但我还是没输过一次
Still, I never lost a fight.
这是南北战争时的事
This has happened during the civil war?
我是德州骑兵最年轻的少校
I was the youngest major in the Texas cavalry.
但从未见识过一场真正的战斗
All without having seen any real battle.
直到
Until…
直到我遇到了一位真正的吸血鬼
Until I met a certain immortal.
玛利亚
Maria.
当时我刚刚疏散了一处的妇孺
I was riding back to Galveston…
正骑马赶回加尔维斯顿
after evacuating a column of women and children.
我一看到她
When I saw her…
就向她提供救援
I immediately offered her my aid.
真可爱 一位军官
Lovely. And an officer.
最好还是你来 玛利亚 我一开始就停不下来
You'd better do it, Maria. I can never stop once I've started.
你叫什么名字 士兵
What's your name, soldier?
贾斯帕·维特洛克少校 女士
Major Jasper Whitlock, Ma'am.
但愿你能幸存
I hope you survive.
你对我来说有很大的用处
You maybe of a great use to me.
玛利亚在制造一支军队吗
Maria was creating an army?
在南方 那很常见
They were very common in the South.
用来争夺领地
And cost a brutal battles for territory.
玛利亚每次都胜利
Maria won them all.
她很聪明 又小心 而且她有了我
She was smart, careful. And she had me.
我是她的副官
I was the second in command.
我控制情绪的能力很合她的胃口
My abilities to control emotions served her well.
我为她训练新生儿
I trained her newborns.
她从不让新生儿活过第一年
An endless occupation since.
那也成了一份无期限的职业
she never let them live beyond their first year.
我的工作也包括清理他们
It was my job to dispose of them.
我可以感受到他们的感受
I could feel everything they felt.
我以为玛利亚和我之间的就是爱
I thought what Maria and I had was love.
但我只是她的木偶 她控制一切
But I was her puppet. She pulled the strings.
我不知道还有别的方式
I didn't know there was another way…
直到我遇见爱丽丝
Until I found Alice.
当然她现在也知道我在说什么
Now she'd seen me coming, of course.
你让我等了好久
Kept me waiting long enough.
我致以歉意 女士
My apologies, Ma'am.
如果没有遇见爱丽丝 真不知道我会变成什么样
I don't know what I'd have become without her.
你再也不用过那样的生活
You'll never have to be that again.
怎么了
What is it?
入侵者
The intruder…
新生吸血鬼军队
The newborn army.
他们都是她的玩偶
They're all her puppets.
维多利亚
Victoria.
如果她造军队 爱丽丝会看到的
Alice would've seen if she wanted to make an army.
如果她把他们藏起来呢
Unless she's hiding behind them,
并且让另外一个人控制军队
and she's letting someone else decide.
欢迎加入军队
Welcome to the army.
我不能在你们为我冒险的时候躲起来
I'm not just gonna hide, while you're taking all the risks for me?
如果此事与维多利亚有关
If it's Victoria involved…
我必须让你远离战场
I need to keep you as far away from the fight as possible.
贾斯帕说我可能会帮上忙
Jasper said that I could be of help.
我们不需要你帮忙
We won't need your help.
有狼人的帮助会赢得很轻松
With the wolves in this, it's an easy win.
我们都没什么可做的
The rest of us, aren't gonna have enough to do.
好吧 到底是情况危险 我必须躲起来
Okay, either it's so dangerous that I have to hide…
还是取胜很容易 以至于你们无所事事
Or it's so easy, that you're gonna be side blind, which is it?
对你来说很危险 对我们来说很轻松
It's dangerous for you. It's easy for us.
我觉得我们分开就会有危险
I think it's dangerous for us to be apart.
我们还需要证明几次呢
How many times we have to prove that?
我会担心 担心你
I'll be worrying. You'll be worried.
我们两个都会恐慌
And we"ll both feel more horrible.
你说得对
Okay, you're right.
所以我要跟着你
So, I'm coming with you.
不 我们必须分开
No, we've got to stay away together.
我不能让你在我和你的家庭之间做选择 只是
I can't make you choose between me and your family, it's…
保护你的唯一办法就是和你在一起
The only way I can protect you, is to be with you.
你们没练习打斗吗
You're not fighting?
还是拉伤肌肉了
What, you pull a muscle or something?
- 他是为了我 - 管他呢
- He's doing it for me. Okay? - Whatever.
告诉我计划吧
Just tell me the plan.
这个地方作为战场对我们十分有利
This field will give us an advantage in battle.
利用贝拉的气味吸引那些新生吸血鬼
We need to lure the newborns with Bella's scent.
必须在这地方结束战斗
It needs to end here.
爱德华和我去营地
Edward and I are going on a campsite.
虽然他和我一起 他们还是能闻到我的气息
Even if he carries me, they'll still pick up our scents.
你的气味实在很恶心
Your stench, however, is revolting.
老兄 你是在逃避气味的优势
Dude, you really don't want to start comparing stinks.
他是说 如果是你带着我 你的气味会遮住我的
What he means, is that your scent will mask mine if you carry me.
说定了
Done.
这不是个好主意
This is not a good idea.
爱德华
Edward.
他们不会接近他的气味
They won't want to get anywhere near his… odor.
好吧 试验一下
Okay, let's just try it.
- 香水狼 来吧 - 跑吧
- Eau de wolf, comin' up. - Run.
你也想让我袖手旁观吗
You gonna ask me to sit out the fight, too?
或者是你不在乎我的安全问题
Or don't you care about my safety?
我当然在意 但是你会拒绝的
Of course I care, but you'd say no.
所以无论如何我没的选择
So I won't have a choice anyways.
自从我让山姆成为领袖
Since I let Sam be alpha male.
就得听从他的召唤
I got to live with the shots he calls.
从你让山姆成为领袖开始吗
Since you let Sam be alpha?
我不想群居 更不用说当他们的领袖了
I didn't want to be in a pack, let alone be it's their leader.
- 雅各布领袖 - 退出了
- Chief Jacob. - Opted out.
但是每个选择都会有结果
But every choice has it's consequences.
- 一些更有意义的选择 - 那就别做选择
- Some more than others. - Don't start.
每个人都有选择 但你必须接受我的
Everybody makes choices, you gonna have to accept mine.
你可以同时爱上多个人
You can love more than one person at a time.
我曾见过 就像山姆 艾米粒和莉亚
I've seen it, with Sam, Emily, and Leah.
- 我不是狼人 我不会留下烙印 - 这跟烙印没关系
- I'm not a wolf, I can't imprint. - It has nothing to do with imprinting.
这和对某人的感觉有关
It has to do with… feeling something for somebody.
我知道你对我有感觉
And I know you feel something for me.
我能感觉到我对你的影响
I can sense how I make you feel…
体会到的
Physically.
我让你紧张了
I make you nervous.
雅各
Jake.
别怕
Don't worry.
除非你要求 我答应过不再吻你
I promised I wouldn't kiss you again until you asked.
那你得一直遵守承诺了 领袖
You're going to be keeping that promise for a while, Chief.
我闻到的只是狼的臭味 没有贝拉的味道
All I picked up was wolf stench. No Bella.
- 这样能行 - 很好
- This will work. - Great.
- 爱丽丝 别见外 - 好
- Okay, Alice. Don't be a stranger. - Okay.
你参加战斗的借口已经搞定了
Your alibi for the battle is all arranged.
是吗
Really?
我告诉你爸爸我们全家周末要去野营
I told your father that our whole family's going camping this weekend.
所以你要在我家住一晚
So you and I are having a sleep over at my house.
- 反正查理要去钓鱼 - 查理吗
- Charlie is going fishing anyway. - Charlie?
你们已经是一路人了吗
You guys run for the same basis now?
他喜欢我
Me, he likes.
实际上 今晚只有你和爱德华在家
Actually, you and Edward will have the house to yourself tonight.
单独吗
Like alone?
我们全要出去打猎 为战斗补充体能
We're all going hunting, powering up for the battle.
不用谢我
You're welcome.
- 来个三明治吗 - 我不饿
- Hey. Do you want a sandwich? - No, I'm good.
他姐姐 我喜欢
Well, the sister… I like.
爱丽丝 她人很好
Alice. Yeah, she's great.
爸爸 我在想
Hey, Dad. I was wondering…
跟妈妈离婚后 为什么不再找一个
Why didn't you get remarried, after Mom?
我不知道
I don't know…
我想还没遇到对的人吧
Guess I still haven't met the right gal.
- 怎么了 - 没什么
- Why? - I don't know.
我以为你只是
I thought you just…
也许你为了传统理念放弃了
Maybe you gave up on the whole institution of it.
婚姻
Of marriage.
但是你想过有何价值吗
But do you think there's any value in it?
婚姻有其价值
Yeah, marriage has value.
你长大后 成熟了
When you're older. Much older.
就像你妈妈那样
Like you're mother…
离婚后似乎过得很好
It seem to work out fine for her the second time round.
- 下半生 - 也许吧
- Later in life. - Yeah, I guess.
我是说
I mean…
你肯定不想结婚
You definitely don't wanna have to get married,
因为你不是很小心
because you weren't… careful.
什么意思
What?
我知道你了解我在说什么
Look, you know what I'm talking about.
有些事你需要好好想想 如果你
There's… Things, that you need to think about it, if you…
如果你们身体很亲密的时候
If you gonna be… physically intimate.
等等 今天谈话到此结束
Okay. Don't… until we've enough of "The Talk".
- 能不说这个吗 - 我也很尴尬
- Don't you just quit. - It's just as embarrassing for me,
- 就跟你一样尴尬 - 我不觉得
- as it is for you. - I doubt that.
别打断 因为妈妈十年前离开的太早
And don't bother, 'cause Mom beat you too early ten years ago.
十年前你也没有男朋友
Well, you didn't have a boyfriend ten years ago.
我想这都一样
I'm sure things work the same way.
好吧 所以
Alright. So…
你们要做些防护措施
You guys are… taking precautions, and…
好了爸爸 请别担心那事儿
Okay, dad. Please just don't worry about that.
爱德华是个保守派
Edward is… old school.
保守派 非常好
Old school, great.
那是什么 某个东西的遗传基因吗
What's that? Like a code for something?
上帝 爸爸
Oh my god. Dad…
我还是处女
I'm a virgin!
好了 走吧 谈得非常好
Okay, go. Glad we covered that.
我也是
Me too.
处女
Virgin…
现在有点儿喜欢爱德华了
Liking Edward a little bit more now.
你在外面干什么呢 怎么了
What are you doing here outside? What's wrong?
没什么
Nothing.
似乎把这个送给你 才算公平一点
It seems the only fair, that I'd be represented as well.
真漂亮
It's really pretty.
谢谢
Thanks.
有一张床呢
There's a bed.
我想你需要睡觉
I thought you might need one to sleep in.
一个充气垫就可以了
I think an air mattress would've sufficed.
- 现在这样不好吗 - 不是
- It is too much? - No.
不 这样很完美
No, it's perfect.
我想知道些事情
I want to ask you something.
洗耳恭听
Anything.
婚姻对你来说是
Okay, marriage is the condition for you,
将我变成你族人的条件 是吗
to change me yourself, right?
是的
Yes.
好 我想谈谈我的条件
Okay. I want to negotiate my own condition.
悉听尊便
Anything you want, It's yours.
你发誓吗
Do you promise?
是的
Yeah.
贝拉 不行
Bella… no.
你说过想让我经历作为人类的一切
You've said that you wanted me to have every human experience.
对你有伤害的就不行
Not the ones that support risk killing you.
你不会伤害我的
You won't.
他们说 一旦我转化后
And everyone says, once I'm changed…
我想做的事就只有杀了城里所有的人
all I'm gonna want is to slaughter the whole town.
这种情况不会持续太久
That part doesn't last forever.
我想要你
I want you.
虽然我没有变 但我还是想这么做
While I'm still me. While I still want you this way.
太危险了
It's too dangerous.
只是试试
Try… Just try.
我会去个可笑奢华的大学
I'll go to some ridiculously expensive college.
然后让你给我买辆车
and let you buy me a car.
我会嫁给你 就试试吧
I'll marry you, just try.
不要把衣服脱下来
Stop trying to take your clothes off.
- 你不想做吗 - 今晚不行
- Do you want to do that part? - Not tonight.
好吧 我是说 你不想
Okay. I mean, you don't…
没关系
But, fine.
相信我 我很想
Believe me, I want to.
我只是想先结婚
I just want to be married to you first.
你真让我觉得 我是个坏女人
You really make me feel like I'm some sort of like a villain trying…
夺走你的贞操之类的东西
steal your virtue or something.
我不是担心我的贞操
It's not my virtue I'm concerned about.
开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
这是个原则 我想把持住
It's just one rule, I wanna leave unbroken.
我的灵魂不再拥有这个原则 但我想让你拥有
It might be too late for my soul, but I will protect yours.
- 我知道这不是个现代观念 - 真不是
- I know it's not a modern notion. - It's not modern.
是古代的
It's ancient.
我来自一个不同的时代
I'm from a different era.
世事并非如此复杂
Things were… a lot less complicated.
如果那时我遇见你 我会向你求爱
And if I met you back then, I would've courted to you.
我们会牵手漫步
We'd have taken chaperoned strolls,
或者在走廊里喝凉茶
or had iced tea on the porch.
我会偷吻你一两次
I may have stolen a kiss or two.
但 只会
But, only…
在征得你父亲的同意之后
after asking your father's permission.
我会单腿下跪
I would've got down on one knee.
还会献上一枚戒指
And I would presented you with a ring.
这曾是我母亲的
This was my mother's.
伊莎贝拉·斯旺 我保证会时时刻刻爱你
Isabella Swan. I promise to love you, every moment forever.
我有此殊荣娶你为妻吗
And would you do me the extraordinary honor of marrying me?
我愿意
Yes.
你不跟我们一起吗
You're not coming with us?
这是千钧一发的时刻
It will be a last minute decision.
我告诉过你怎么做
I told you how it works.
卡伦一家有神奇的力量
The Cullens have powers.
别低估了他们 莱利
Don't underestimate them, Riley.
你有军队
You'll have the numbers,
但是他们能够
but they'll be able to…
预见你每一步
anticipate your every move.
- 你朋友这么说的吗 - 是
- According to your friend. - Yes.
我死去的朋友
My dead friend.
劳伦发现了他们的行动
Laurent found out about the things they could do,
他们就杀了他
and they killed him.
可我知道得太晚
But not before he told me.
也许他错了
Maybe he was wrong.
我是说
I mean…
这应该是
This is supposed to be…
卡伦家族的领地
Cullen territory.
但是我们已经侵入 却仍未见他们的踪影
But we've been tearing it up and I've never even seen them here.
你不相信我
You don't trust me.
我用生命爱你 我只是说
With my life. I'm just saying that…
我是为了我们可以不再挨饿
I'm doing this for us. So that we can feed,
不用担心他们的报复 再也不用害怕了
without their retaliation. Can't live in fear anymore,
再也不用坐以待毙了
waiting for them to attack.
我不会让他们得逞的
I won't let them.
我现在就去结束卡伦家族
I'm going to end the Cullen clan.
我发誓
I swear.
我太爱你了
I love you. So much.
你这样做很傻
You're going overboard.
如果只能做这些 我想坚持到底
If this is all I can contribute, I want to be thorough.
新生吸血鬼会为此而疯狂的
The newborns will be frantic.
没事儿 别难过
It's Okay. Don't make yourself uncomfortable.
我不会再发火了
It doesn't bother me anymore.
从何时开始
Since when?
自从以为你死了之后的24小时
Since I spent 24 hours thinking you were dead.
你没带戒指
You're not wearing your ring.
我怕弄丢了
Well, I didn't want to risk losing it.
或者是怕雅各布看见吧
Or risk Jacob seeing it?
我想应该等等再告诉他
I think we should wait to tell him.
至少等这场战斗之后
I mean, at least till after the fight.
- 你是否有别的想法 - 不 我没有
- If you're having second thoughts… - I'm not.
我只是不想让他分神
I just want him to have a clear head.
谁分神了
Whose head is unclear?
我想没人
Nobody's, I hope.
爱丽丝说风暴要来临了
Alice says there's a storm coming.
我能感觉到 我们应该走了
Yeah, I can feel it. We should get going.
几小时后见
I'll see you in a couple of hours.
出什么事了吗
Something up?
一群吸血鬼想杀了我
A bunch of vampires trying to kill me.
老调重弹
Same old, same old.
谢谢
Thank you.
暴风雪就要来了 你快回去吧
You should get back before the storm hits.
不 我留下
No, I'm staying.
我会帮你和狼群取得联系
You'll need my connection to the pack,
密切关注任何风吹草动
to keep tabs on what's going on.
- 你不参加战斗了 - 明早赛斯会来接我的班
- You're not going to fight? - Seth will spell me in the morning.
他一直对这个安排耿耿于怀
He's not happy about missing the action,
但这能保证他平安无事
but it'll keep him out of trouble.
我们快进去吧
Let's get you inside.
应该找个海拔低一点的地方
I should have chosen a site lower down.
没事 我很好
No, It's fine. I'm okay.
我能为你做什么
What can I do?
牙齿打架的声音吵得我根本睡不着
I can't sleep with all that teeth chattering going on.
你休想
Forget it.
我可不想她把脚都冻掉了 你得承认
She may need her toes someday. And let's face it…
我比你温暖
I'm hotter than you.
把手拿开
Get your hand off me!
你不许碰她
Get your hands off her!
别打架
Don't fight.
她病了 你看着办
She gets sick, it's on you.
你冻僵了 贝拉
Why! You're freezing, Bella.
放松 马上就能暖起来
Relax, You'll warm up soon.
要是你脱掉衣服能暖得更快
Faster if you took your clothes off.
- 雅各 - 《幸存者101》里说的
- Jake. - Survival one oh one.
你能不能试着控制下你的思绪
Can you, at least attempt to control your thoughts?
你真被我惹毛了是吗
I really get under that ice cold skin of yours, don't I?
怎么了
What?
你在怀疑她对你的感情
Are you doubting her feelings for you?
好吧
Nice…
你偷窥我的想法 没问题
So picking through my brain's okay,
可让我猜你的心思 还是省省吧
but letting me into yours, forget it.
听着
Look…
- 我知道她爱你 - 太好了
- I know she's in love with you. - Oh, good.
可她也爱着我
But she's in love with me, too.
她只是不愿承认
She just won't admit it to herself.
她怎么想我不清楚
I can't tell you if you're right.
我问你
Then let me ask you something.
- 要是她选择了我 - 不会的
- If she chooses me… - She won't.
我是说当初
If she did.
你会杀了我吗
Would you try to kill me?
这主意听起来不错
That's an intriguing idea.
可我不会 我不会那样伤害她
But no. I couldn't hurt her like that.
你只想把她变成和你一样的嗜血恶魔
See, you'd just turn her into a bloodsucking demon like you.
我不想 从来都没想过
I don't want that. I never wanted that.
- 那就阻止她 - 我试过
- So stop her. - I tried.
- 我离开了她 - 可你回来得太快了
- I left. - But you gave up too quickly.
要是你再多消失半年
If you'd stayed away another six months,
我会让她很幸福 相信我
I could've made her happy. Trust me.
你得想想
You have to consider…
我可能比你更适合她
that I might be better for her than you are.
我想过
I have considered that.
我知道你能保护她
I know you can protect her.
你能让她过上正常的人类生活
But you can give her a life, a human life.
那是我对她最大的愿望
It's all I want for her.
可我不会
But, I'm not…
我不会再逼迫她做任何事情 再也不会
I'm not going to force her into anything, ever again.
上一次让我们两个都差点送了命
The last time I tried, it almost killed us both.
是呀 我记得
Yeah, that I remember.
那个时候 当你认为她已经死了
When you thought she was gone…
你已经失去她了
that you'd lost her…
你是怎样的
How did you… cope?
无法形容
There're no words.
可我不会让任何人和我分担这份痛苦 雅各布
But I wouldn't wash it on anyone, Jacob.
说来奇怪 不过我挺高兴你能在这
This might sound odd, but I'm glad you're here.
不错
Pretty neat.
比起杀了你 我更希望她温暖
As much as I'd love to kill you, I'm glad she's warm.
如果我们不是天生的敌人
If we weren't natural enemies…
而你也不一直非要剥夺我存在的理由
and you weren't trying to steal my reason for existing…
我会很喜欢你
I might actually like you.
好吧
Well…
如果你不想吸干我深爱的女孩的生命
If you weren't planning on sucking the life out of the girl I love,
我会
I might…
不 那我也不会
No… Not even then.
她还能改变主意
But she could still change her mind, you know.
那我就放手
Then I'd let her go.
早 赛斯
Fine. Hi, Seth.
雅各布去哪了 他已经
Where's Jacob? Did he already…
还没
Not yet.
他走之前要检查森林里是否安全
He's checking to see if the woods are clear before he goes.
昨晚的事 真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry about last night.
我应该理解你的
I couldn't have been easy on you.
昨晚绝不会进入我十大最爱夜晚榜单
It definitely won't make my list of top ten favorite evenings.
你还有个榜单
You have a list?
十个和你共度的夜晚
All ten I spent with you.
第一名就是你同意求婚的那天
Number one is when you said you'd marry me.
卡伦夫人
Mrs. Cullen.
现在已经21世纪了
This is the twenty-first century,
我想保留我的姓
I always wanna hyphenate my name.
你要嫁给他吗
You're marrying him?
雅各
Jake…
你知道他在听
You knew he was listening?
他应该知道
He deserves to know.
- 雅各 等等 - 贝拉 别去
- Jake, stop! - Bella, let him…
放开
Don't!
雅各 等等
Jake, stop!
- 雅各 我求你 - 我累了 非常累
- Jake, please! - I'm done! I'm so done!
- 我能为你做些什么 - 你什么都做不了
- What can I do? - You can't do anything.
可我能 下去和那些魔鬼拼个你死我活
I can. By going out there and killing something.
不 你镇静一下 别冲动
No! You're not thinking clearly, don't do that!
或许我死了 你就不用左右为难
Maybe I'll get my self killed and make it simple for you.
不 雅各 别走
No! Just, Jake… Stay!
为什么
Why?
给我一个充分的理由
Give me one good reason.
因为我不想失去你
Because I don't wanna lose you.
不够充分
It's not good enough.
因为你对我很重要
Because you're too important.
还是不够充分
Still not good enough.
雅各布
Jacob!
吻我
Kiss me!
我叫你吻我
I'm asking you to kiss me.
这是我们的初吻
That should have been our first kiss.
我得走了
I gotta go.
我会回来的
I'll be back.
你都看到了
You saw.
没有 可雅各布想得太多了
No. But Jacob's thoughts are very loud.
我不知道我怎么了
I don't know what happened.
你爱他
You love him.
我更爱你
I love you more.
我知道
I know.
战斗开始了
It's starting.
雅各布到了
Jacob just got there.
他没事
He's good.
有人受伤吗
Someone's hurt?
她在附近 我能听到她
She's close. I can hear her thoughts.
赛斯快离开
Seth, go.
她知道我们不在那 她闻到了我的气味
She knew we weren't there, but she caught my scent.
她知道你一定跟我在一起
She knew you'd be with me.
她找到我们了
She found us.
她有同伙
She's not alone.
莱利 听我说
Riley… Listen to me.
维多利亚在利用你 来分散我的注意力
Victoria's just using you, to distract me.
她知道我会杀了你
But she knows I'll kill you.
而且 她还很高兴之后你就不会再纠缠她了
In fact, she'll be glad she doesn't have to deal with you anymore.
别听他的 莱利
Don't listen, Riley.
我跟你说过他读心的把戏
I told you about their mind tricks.
我能读到她的想法 我知道她怎么想你
I can read her mind, so I know what she thinks of you.
他在撒谎
He's lying.
她创造你和军队 只为给她的的真爱詹姆斯报仇
She only created you and this army to avenge her true mate, James.
那才是她真正在乎的 不是你
It's the only thing she cares about. Not you.
我爱的只有你 你知道的
There's only you. You know that.
想想吧
Think about it.
你生长在福克斯 你熟悉地形
You're from Forks, you know the area.
这才是她选择你的真正原因
That's the only reason she chose you.
她不爱你
She doesn't love you.
莱利
Riley…
不要信他的挑拨离间
Don't let him do this to us.
你知道我爱你
You know I love you.
你死定了
You're dead.
你跑了就再也没有机会了
You won't get another chance like this again.
你想要她性命
You want her!
你想让我也感受丧失爱人的痛苦
You want me to feel the pain you felt when I killed James.
就像当我把詹姆斯大卸八块
When I tore him to pieces.
把他抽筋扒皮 挫骨扬灰时
When I turned him into ash.
你感受的那样
When I turned him into nothing.
维多利亚
Victoria!
- 有情况吗 - 爱丽丝要我们过去
- Something's wrong. - Alice needs us to go.
现在
And now.
- 还有多久 - 几分钟 大概十分钟
- How long? - A few minutes. Maybe ten.
狼群必须离开
The pack needs to leave.
沃尔图里家族可不会喜欢和狼人的休战协定
The Volturi won't honor a truce with the werewolves.
莉亚 不要
Leah, don't!
雅各布
Jacob!
雅各布 坚持住 卡莱尔会照顾你
Jacob. Hold on, Carlisle is gonna take care of you.
身体右侧的骨骼全部粉碎
The bones on the right half of his body are shattered.
- 贝拉 - 雅各 我在这
- Bella. - Jake, I'm right here.
- 雅各布你个白痴 我能行的 - 莉亚
- Jacob, you idiot. I had it. - Leah.
我得在他开始愈合前将骨骼正位
I need to set the bones before his accelerated healing kicks in.
- 已经开始了 - 得让他离开这
- It's already starting. - We need to get him out of here.
我们没把握能打赢沃尔图里家族
We're not gonna win a fight with the Volturi.
- 我们带他去比利那 - 我会尽快赶到的
- We'll take him back to Billy's. - I'll be there as soon as I can.
坚持住 雅各
Hang in there, Jake.
会没事的
We got you.
他们来了
They're coming.
精彩之极
Impressive.
我还没见过哪个族群
I've never seen a coven.
能在如此猛烈的进攻中全身而退
Escape an assault of this magnitude intact.
运气而已
We were lucky.
深表怀疑
I doubt that.
貌似我们错过了一场有趣的战斗
It appears we missed an entertaining fight.
是呀 好像我们突然变得无关紧要了
Yes. It's not often we're rendered unnecessary.
要是你们早来半个小时 就能如愿以偿了
If you'd arrived a half hour ago, you would've fulfilled your purpose.
真是遗憾
Pity.
你们落下一个
You missed one.
我们同意她投降 会收容她
We offered her asylum in exchange for her surrender.
你们没有这个资格
That wasn't yours to offer.
你们为何而来
Why did you come?
谁创造了你们
Who created you?
你没必要折磨她
You don't need to do that.
她会告诉你想知道的一切
She'll tell you anything you want to know.
我知道
I know.
我不知道
I don't know.
莱利不告诉我们
Riley wouldn't tell us.
他说我们的思想不安全
He said our thoughts weren't safe.
她叫维多利亚 你或许认识
Her name was Victoria. Perhaps you knew her.
爱德华 要是沃尔图里家族知道维多利亚的事
Edward. If the Volturi had knowledge of Victoria,
他们会阻止她的
they would've stopped her.
没错吧 简
Isn't that right, Jane?
当然
Of course.
菲利克斯
Felix.
无知者无罪
She didn't know what she was doing.
我们会对她负责
We'll take responsibility for her.
给她一次机会
Give her a chance.
沃尔图里家族不会恩赐第二次机会
The Volturi don't give second chances.
这一点一定要铭记
Keep that in mind.
卡鲁斯若知道她还是人类 会很感兴趣的
Caius will be interested to know that she's still human.
日期已经确定了
The date is set.
交给你了 菲利克斯
Take care of that, Felix.
我想回家了
I'd like to go home.
- 已经有一阵子了 - 医生得把骨头重新打折
- It's been going on for a while. - Doc's rebreaking his bones.
他为什么要掺和进来 我自己就能捏死那
Why'd he have to butt in? I could've taken that tick…
歇歇吧 莉亚
Oh, give it a rest, Leah.
最糟糕的过去了 他会没事的
The worst is over. He'll be alright.
我给他用了吗啡
I gave him some morphine,
但他的体温会使其很快挥发掉
but his body temperature will burn it off soon.
我会回来给他输液的
I'll come back to set up a drip.
谢谢
Thank you.
他找你
He's asking for you.
雅各
Hey, Jake.
我很担心你
I was worried about you.
你担心我
You were worried about me?
是
Yeah.
我猜爱德华读到了我的想法
I guessed Edward would read my thoughts.
他难为你了吗
Was he hard on you?
他不恨我 也不恨你
He wasn't even mad at me. Or you.
该死
Well, damn.
他比我想象的好得多
He's better than I thought.
他是认真的
He's not playing a game.
好吧
Right.
贝拉
Bella…
他不像你想的那样完美
He's not as perfect as you think.
我知道他是谁
I know who he is.
我不该说这些
I must not talk about that.
长痛不如短痛
I'd rather get all the rebreaking done at once.
至少我知道自己尽力了
At least I know I did everything I could.
让你承认你对我的感情可真不容易
Wasn't easy making you admit your feelings for me.
我一直克制自己
I only fought them,
我知道这感情改变不了什么
Because I know they wouldn't change anything.
我才是最适合你的 贝拉
I'm exactly right for you, Bella.
和我在一起会像呼吸般自然简单
It would be as easy as breathing with me.
你知道我爱你
You know I love you.
我多想这样就足够了
You know how much I wish it was enough.
我能再来吗
Should I come back?
我需要些时间
I need some time.
我会一直等你
But I'll always be waiting.
直到我停止心跳
Untill my heart stops beating.
那之后也依然等
Maybe even then.
- 8月13日吗 - 没错
- August thirteenth? - Yeah.
我生日前一个月
it's a month before my birthday.
我不想再比你老一岁了
I don't need to be another year older than you.
爱丽丝说她能搞定婚礼的
Alice said she can get the wedding together by then.
她肯定能
I'm sure she can.
不用急的
There's no rush.
我选择了我的生活 我想要马上开始
I've chosen my life. I want to start living it.
你想让爱丽丝操办整个婚事
And so, you're gonna let Alice plan the whole thing?
是呀
Yeah.
着装 接待 来宾名单
Dress, the reception, the guest list…
谁知道她会邀请谁
I mean, who knows who she's gonna invite?
这重要吗
Does it matter?
我不知道你为何这样做
I just don't know why you're doing this.
什么 婚礼吗
What? The wedding?
你试着让身边的所有人快乐
You're trying to make everyone else happy.
可你放弃太多了
But you're already giving away too much.
你错了
You're wrong.
这不是你和雅各布间的抉择
This wasn't a choice between you and Jacob.
而是真我和现在的我之间的抉择
It was between who I should be and who I am.
我总是觉得步调不协调
I've always felt out of step.
在生活中跌跌撞撞
Like literally, stumbling through my life.
所有人都觉得我不正常
I'm never felt normal.
因为我就是不正常
Because I'm not normal.
我不想正常
I don't wanna be.
在你的世界中
I've had to face death…
我不得不面对死亡 失去和痛苦
and loss and pain, in your world.
可同时 我也会更强壮
But, I've also never felt stronger…
更真实 更自我
more real, more… my self.
因为那也是我的世界
Because it's my world, too.
是我本该属于的地方
It's where I belong.
这么说 不只是因为我
So, it's not just about me.
抱歉 不是
No, sorry.
思考这些曾让我焦头烂额
I've made a mess trying to figure all this out, but…
可我想找到正解
I wanna do it right.
我也想和你紧紧连在一起
And I wanna tie my self to you,
以所有可能的人类的方式
in every way humanly possible.
从婚礼开始
Starting with a wedding.
事实上
Actually…
应该是始于一些更困难的事情
Something, a little more difficult first.
或许也是更危险的
And maybe even dangerous.
我们得先告诉查理
We have to tell Charlie.
那是相当危险
It's highly dangerous.
幸好你是防弹的
It's a good thing you're bulletproof.
把戒指给我吧
I'm gonna need that ring.